Philip K. Crowe Papers MS109
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Embassy, Government and Military Papers, 1930 -- 1976; 1941 -- 1975; MS109.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  - Military War Records: Change of Station, 1942 -- 1945; MS109.003.038.00003 (Box 38)
  - Military War Record: Temp Duty, 1942 -- 1945; MS109.003.038.00004 (Box 38)
  - Military War Records: Leave, 1942 -- 1944; MS109.003.038.00005 (Box 38)
  - Military War Record: Pay, 1942 -- 1945; MS109.003.038.00006 (Box 38)
  - Military War Record: Medical Information, 1935 -- 1944; MS109.003.038.00007 (Box 38)
  - Military War Record: Air Force Reserve, 1947 -- 1955; MS109.003.038.00008 (Box 38)
  - Military War Record: Army Qualification Records, 1944 -- 1945; MS109.003.038.00009 (Box 38)
  - Military War Record: Army Records and Personal History Statement, 1942 -- 1952; MS109.003.038.00010 (Box 38)
  - Executive Branch Liaison Office The White House, Quotes, 1953 -- 1954; MS109.003.038.00011 (Box 38)
    Quotes, excerpts and full text of speeches given by President Eisenhower.
  - Executive Branch Liaison Office The White House, Quotes, 1954 -- 1957; MS109.003.038.00012 (Box 38)
  - Executive Branch Liaison Office The White House, Fact Papers, 1953 -- 1955; MS109.003.038.00013 (Box 38)
    Fact Papers were newsletters circulated among presidential appointees to enable them to follow the evolution of policy for the Eisenhower administration.
  - Executive Branch Liaison Office The White House, Fact Papers, 1955 -- 1956; MS109.003.038.00014 (Box 38)
  - Executive Branch Liaison Office The White House, Fact Papers, 1956; MS109.003.038.00015 (Box 38)
  - Executive Branch Liaison Office The White House, Fact Papers, 1956 -- 1957; MS109.003.038.00016 (Box 38)
  - US Information Agency: Advance Briefing Material, December, 1960; MS109.003.038.00017 (Box 38)
  - Guest Book: US Embassy, Oslo, Norway, 1969 -- 1972; MS109.003.038.00018 (Box 38)
  - Guest Book: American Embassy Copenhagen, Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00019 (Box 38)
    Volume 37 of the Diaries.
  - Department of State Press Release: Crowe Appointment to Denmark, 1973; MS109.003.038.00020 (Box 38)
    Press release anouncing the swearing in of Philip K. Crowe as the Ambassador to Denmark.
  - Photographs, Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00021 (Box 38)
    Photographs of Rydhave, the ambassadorial residence, Copenhagen, Denmark.
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00022 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00023 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00024 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00025 (Box 38)
  - Photographs Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00026 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00027 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00028 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00029 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00030 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00031 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00032 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00033 (Box 38)
  - Photographs: Rydhave, US Embassy Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00034 (Box 38)
  - Chief of Mission Briefing Book, Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00035 (Box 38)
    Notes concerning the country of Denmark, the US embassy, protocol, the ambassadorial residence including floor plan, and security
  - Organizational Briefing Book, American Embassy Copenhagen, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00036 (Box 38)
    Notes on the staff of the American Embassy Copenhagen Denmark.
  - Telephone Directory American Embassy Copenhagen, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00037 (Box 38)
  - Collection of Articles on Greenland, 1972; MS109.003.038.00038 (Box 38)
  - Thule Air Base, Greenland, 1974; MS109.003.038.00039 (Box 38)
    Press release, article and photographs concerning Crowe's visit to Thule Air Base.
  - Greenland Visit, 1974; MS109.003.038.00040 (Box 38)
  - Manuscript: Ascension Island by L. S. Bartlett, MS109.003.038.00041 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Diplomatic Corp and List of Individuals for Embassy Parties, 1974 -- 1975; MS109.003.038.00042 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Embassy, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00043 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Social, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00044 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Royal Court, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00045 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Diplomatic Corps, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00046 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Cabinet, 1975 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00047 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Ministries, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00048 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Mayors and Cities, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00049 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Governors, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00050 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Police and Courts, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00051 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Parliament, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00052 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Arts and Sciences, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00053 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Military, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00054 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Press, 1973 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00055 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Greenland, 1974 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00056 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Faeroe Islands, 1974 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00057 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: Bornholm, 1974 -- 1976; MS109.003.038.00058 (Box 38)
  - Embassy Entertainment Binder: "To Say Goodbye" Reception, 1975; MS109.003.038.00059 (Box 38)
- Photographs, 1800 -- 1981; 1944 -- 1975; MS109.004; 5.8 Linear Feet; 36 Digital Object(s)
  This series includes portraits, photographs, and negatives documenting Philip K. Crowe's life and diplomatic career between 1944 and 1975. Some of the framed portraits include signed dedications to Ambassador Philip K. Crowe. Tufts University administrators, Dean Rusk and Dean Peterson, are among these portraits. There are also signed portraits of Richard Nixon, Lyndon Johnson, and Harry S. Truman. The portraits originally adorned the Crowe Room at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy.
  The photographs consist of official press photographs, game hunting photographs, and personal family photographs. There is also one folder of photograph negatives, including negatives of photographs taken for articles written by Crowe.
  - Photographs: Africa, MS109.004.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Africa, MS109.004.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Africa, MS109.004.039.00003 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Africa, Hunting, MS109.004.039.00004 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Africa, Hunting, MS109.004.039.00005 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Africa, Hunting, MS109.004.039.00006 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Fishing, MS109.004.039.00007 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Hunting, MS109.004.039.00008 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Hunting, MS109.004.039.00009 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, Yvonne December, 1912 -- 1960; MS109.004.039.00010 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, Yvonne, MS109.004.039.00011 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, Family, MS109.004.039.00012 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, Family, MS109.004.039.00013 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, Family, MS109.004.039.00014 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, Family, MS109.004.039.00015 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, MS109.004.039.00016 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, MS109.004.039.00017 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, MS109.004.039.00018 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, MS109.004.039.00019 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Personal Photographs, MS109.004.039.00020 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Casual Photographs of Philip K. Crowe, MS109.004.039.00021 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Equestrian Photographs, MS109.004.039.00022 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Formal Portraits, Philip K. Crowe, MS109.004.039.00023 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Air Force Missile Test Center, Patrick Air Force Base, Florida, 1960; MS109.004.039.00024 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Photographs and Materials from Wild Life, 1972; MS109.004.039.00025 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Arrival at Department of State, 1956; MS109.004.039.00026 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Copenhagen, Denmark Residence, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.004.039.00027 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Philip and Irene Crowe, MS109.004.039.00028 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Crowe and Charles W. Eifler, MS109.004.039.00029 (Box 39)
  - Crowe Portraits in State Dress, MS109.004.039.00030 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00031 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Group Photographs of Crowe with Unidentified People, MS109.004.039.00032 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Maharaja of Mysore, MS109.004.039.00033 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Oil Rig, MS109.004.039.00034 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Conference Aboard USS Midway, MS109.004.039.00035 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Ceylon, 1953 -- 1956; MS109.004.039.00036 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Unidentified Copenhagen, Denmark, 1973 -- 1975; MS109.004.039.00037 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified Oslo Norway, 1969 -- 1973; MS109.004.039.00038 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs Oslo, Norway, 1969 -- 1973; MS109.004.039.00039 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Norway, 1969 -- 1973; MS109.004.039.00040 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Norway, 1969 -- 1973; MS109.004.039.00041 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, Norway, 1969 -- 1973; MS109.004.039.00042 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs Cape Town, South Africa, 1959 -- 1961; MS109.004.039.00043 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, Johannesburg, South Africa, 1959 -- 1961; MS109.004.039.00044 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00045 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00046 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00047 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00048 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00049 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00050 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00051 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00052 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00053 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00054 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00055 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00056 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00057 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00058 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00059 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00060 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00061 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00062 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00063 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00064 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00065 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00066 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00067 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00068 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.039.00069 (Box 39)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Crowe and Unidentified, MS109.004.040.00001 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Unidentified, MS109.004.040.00002 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Unidentified, MS109.004.040.00003 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Unidentified, MS109.004.040.00004 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Unidentified, MS109.004.040.00005 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Press Photographs, Proofs, MS109.004.040.00006 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: US Navy Press Photographs, MS109.004.040.00007 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: US Navy Press Photographs, 1970 -- 1980; MS109.004.040.00008 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Sir John Kotelawala and Crowe, MS109.004.040.00009 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Swearing in Ceremony, Union of South Africa, 1959; MS109.004.040.00010 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Swearing in Ceremony, Denmark, 1969; MS109.004.040.00011 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Swearing in Ceremony, Norway, 1973; MS109.004.040.00012 (Box 40)
  - Photographs:Tunku Abdul Rahman and Crowe, MS109.004.040.00013 (Box 40)
  - Photograph: Unidentified, Uganda Protectorate, MS109.004.040.00014 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: USS Forrestal Aircrafts, MS109.004.040.00015 (Box 40)
  - USS Lake Champlain Reception, 1953; MS109.004.040.00016 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: USS Hornet at Colombo, Ceylon, 1954; MS109.004.040.00017 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: USS Wasp Visit, 1970; MS109.004.040.00018 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Visitof the Ceylonese Prime Minister to the USA, 1954; MS109.004.040.00019 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Whaler Bound for Tromso, Norway, MS109.004.040.00020 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Yuveraj Karan Singh of Kashmir, MS109.004.040.00021 (Box 40)
  - Framed Photographs: Philip K. Crowe and Trophy, 1961; MS109.004.040.00022 (Box 40)
  - Framed Photographs: Unidentified Male, Nepal, 1954; MS109.004.040.00023 (Box 40)
  - Framed Photographs: Unidentified Female, MS109.004.040.00024 (Box 40)
  - Framed Photographs: Crowe Posing with Snake, MS109.004.040.00025 (Box 40)
  - Framed Photographs: Crowe with 20 in Brown Trout, 1968; MS109.004.040.00026 (Box 40)
  - Framed Photographs: Philip K. Crowe, Formal Portrait, MS109.004.040.00027 (Box 40)
  - Framed Photographs: Philip K. Crowe Formal Portrait, 1969; MS109.004.040.00028 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Article Norwegian Racing Jubilee, Ovrevoll Race Course, MS109.004.040.00029 (Box 40)
  - Photographs: Crowe, MS109.004.040.00030 (Box 40)
  - Philip Crowe in Norway, 1970; MS109.004.040.00031 (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 1 of numbered photographs.
    Men; Portraits; photographic print; Crowe, Philip K.
  - Philip Crowe with a fish, MS109.004.040.00032; Unknown (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 2 of numbered photographs.
    Fish; Men; photographic print; Crowe, Philip K.
  - Philip Crowe hunting in Easton, Maryland, MS109.004.040.00033; Unknown (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 3 of numbered photographs.
    Hunting; Hunting Dogs; Men; Trees; photographic print; Crowe, Philip K.
  - Mohan Shamshur, Maharaja of Nepal, MS109.004.040.00034; Unknown (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 26 of numbered photographs.
    Portraits; Swords; Military uniforms; photographic print; Shamsur, Mohan
  - Sri Prakasa, MS109.004.040.00035 (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 27 of numbered photographs.
    Portraits; Governors; photographic print; Prakasa, Sri
  - Farid Didi, Sultan of the Maldive Islands, MS109.004.040.00036; Unknown (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 29 of numbered photographs.
    Portraits; Men; photographic print; Didi, Farid
  - Sir John Kotelawala, MS109.004.040.00037; Sumathipala, Victor (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 30 of numbered photographs.
    Prime Minister; Military uniforms; Portraits; photographic print; Kotelawala, Sir John
  - Philip Crowe in Woodstock, Vermont, MS109.004.040.00038 (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 34 of numbered photographs.
    Portraits; Men; photographic print; Crowe, Philip K.
  - Philip Crowe in ambassabor's uniform, MS109.004.040.00039; Stahnke, J. (Box 40)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 40 of numbered photographs.
    Ambassadors; Military uniforms; Portraits; photographic print; Crowe, Philip K.
  - Negative: Assorted Negatives, MS109.004.040.00040 (Box 40)
  - Negatives: Philip K. Crowe in Easton, Maryland, MS109.004.040.00041 (Box 40)
  - Negative: Philip K. Crowe and Portrait, 1970; MS109.004.040.00042 (Box 40)
  - Negatives: Philip K. Crowe and Dogs, MS109.004.040.00043 (Box 40)
  - Negatives: Philip and Irene Crowe with Cat, MS109.004.040.00044 (Box 40)
  - Negatives: Crowe and His Horse, MS109.004.040.00045 (Box 40)
  - Negatives: Photographs for Articles, MS109.004.040.00046 (Box 40)
  - Slides: Wildlife, Africa, MS109.004.040.00047 (Box 40)
  - Photo Album, 1960; MS109.004.041 (Box 41)
    Photo Album detailing the visit of Their Majesties the King and Queen of Denmark to the United States, October 4 to 17, 1960
  - Oversize Framed Photographs, Armorial Bearings, and Drawings, 1944 -- 1960; MS109.004.045.00001 (Box 45)
    The box contains oversize photographs of Philip K. Crowe big game hunting in Indore State, Bechuanaland (Africa), Mysore, Ceylon, and South Africa. Also included are images of natives, a portrait of Fairfield Osborn, and portraits of Philip K. Crowe. The Crowe family armorial bearings are included as well. Also there are drawings of cock fights by P.E.P. Deraniyagala.
  - Certificate of Appointment, Ambassador to Denmark, July 16, 1973; MS109.004.046.00001 (Box 46)
    Certificate originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 4 of numbered photographs.
    Ambassadors; Certificate; Presidents--United States; Crowe, Philip K.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-
  - Certificate of Appointment, Ambassador to Norway, May 1, 1969; MS109.004.046.00002 (Box 46)
    Certificate originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 5 of numbered photographs.
  - Certificate of Appointment Ambassador to Union of South Africa, February 16, 1959; MS109.004.046.00003 (Box 46)
    Certificate originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 6 of numbered photographs.
    Ambassadors; Certificate; Presidents--United States; Crowe, Philip K.; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969
  - Autographed Photograph of David Schnell, 1970; MS109.004.046.00004 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 9 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Schnell, David
  - Autographed Photograph of Dean Acheson, 1965; MS109.004.046.00005 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 10 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Politician; Acheson, Dean Gooderham; Crowe, Philip K.
  - Autographed Photograph of Douglas Dillon, 1959; MS109.004.046.00006 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 11 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Politician; Dillon, Clarence Douglas
  - Autographed Photograph of John Foster Dulles, 1959; MS109.004.046.00007 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 13 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Politician; Dulles, John Foster
  - Autographed Photograph of Christian Archibald Herter, 1959; MS109.004.046.00008 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 14 of numbered photographs. The signature is faded and slightly illegible.
    People; Portraits; Herter, Christian Archibald
  - Autographed Photograph of Henry A. Kissinger, 1975; MS109.004.046.00009 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 15 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Politician; Scholars; Kissinger, Henry Alfred
  - Autographed Photograph of Stefano Scinici [?], 1970; MS109.004.046.00010 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 16 of numbered photographs. The signature is slightly illegible.
    People; Portraits; photographic print; Crowe, Philip K.
  - Autographed Photograph of William P. Rogers, 1970; MS109.004.046.00011 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 17 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Rogers, William P.
  - Autographed Photograph of Dean Rusk, 1965; MS109.004.046.00012 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 18 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Politician; Rusk, David Dean
  - Autographed Photograph of Harry S. Truman, 1955; MS109.004.046.00013 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 19 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Presidents--United States; Truman, Harry S.
  - Autographed Photograph of Lydon Johnson, 1963; MS109.004.046.00014 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 20 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Presidents--United States; Johnson, Lyndon Baines
  - Autographed Photograph of Richard M. Nixon, 1970; MS109.004.046.00015 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 21 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Presidents--United States; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-
  - Autographed Photograph of Philip Crowe and Jaya Chamaraya Wadyar, 1956; MS109.004.046.00016 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 22 of numbered photographs. On back: "Presented to Philip K. Crowe, American Ambassador to Ceylon, by his Highness the Maharaja of Mysore, India, 1956.
    People; Portraits; Wadyar, Jaya Chamaraja
  - Autographed Photograph of Philip Crowe and Muhammed Ali Borga, Prime Minister of Pakistan, 1954; MS109.004.046.00017 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 23 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Borga, Muhammed Ali, 1909-1963
  - Autographed Photograph of Philip Crowe and Jawaharlal Nehru Prime Minister of India, 1954; MS109.004.046.00018 (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Frame 24 of numbered photographs.
    People; Portraits; Nehru, Jawaharlal
  - Autographed photograph of Viscount Soulbury, Govenor-General of Ceylon, 1954; MS109.004.046.00019; Unknown (Box 46)
    Photograph originally displayed in the Crowe Room in Ginn Library. Includes handwritten note glued to original frame backing. The frame is somewhat water damaged and the note has started to detach partially.
    People; Portraits; image/tiff; Soulbury, Herwald Ramsbotham, Lord, 1887-1971; Crowe, Philip K.
  - Autographed Photograph of Sir Oliver Goonetilleke, Governor-General Ceylon, 1956; MS109.004.046.00020 (Box 46)